Marc T Stukes

202 Cloverbrook dr Jamestown, NC 27282 (702)808-3206 Marcstukesnyc@gmail.com

Skills

I have 20 years of experience in sales, marketing and customer service. I also have 14 years of computer programming, IT solutions and web development. During this time of growth I have retained a number of skills and was provided training in many different industries. These skills include sales, marketing, affiliate marketing management, Microsoft, IOS, Linux, computer programming, web design, crm, data, IP services, call center customer service, wireless services(sales and tech support), business development and computer network management.

Experience

September 2019 - March 2020

Conduit Global, McLeansville, NC - *Verizon wireless Tech support/ Contact Representative*

Conduit Global is a direct contact center for Verizon Wireless. As a contact representative my duties are tier one wireless tech support, sales and customer service. I also have extensive training in Verizon wireless platform ACSS and CRM systems.

April 2011 - June 2019

Creative Business Services, Las Vegas, NV - Business Development Consultant

As a consultant and sales representative at Creative Business Services I worked with new and existing businesses in regards to their company structure. My main focus was educating business owners on the benefits of incorporating their business and establishing business credit for funding. I would also assist in the set up of the company structure and market other products and services provided by the company. In 2015 I began to work remotely for Creative Business Services until I parted with the company in 2019.

June 2009 - March 2011

Global Healthcare, Las vegas, NV - Customer service

Global Healthcare was a brokerage company for health insurance providers. As a full time customer service representative I would provide information about available health insurance plans based on customer income and family needs.

February 2007 - May 2009

Westgate Resort, Las Vegas ,NV - Reservations

Westgate Resort is a vacation ownership resort with destinations worldwide. While at Westgate I booked reservations for our guests and also was involved in the marketing campaign for the new property in Las Vegas.

March 2004 - January 2006

Smart City, Las Vegas, NV

Smart City is an IT solutions company that provides troubleshooting and internet access for most of the major tech related conventions in the city of Las Vegas. While at Smart City our company provided IT solutions for CES,Comdex and many others. We were also responsible for troubleshooting any connectivity issues for all vendors present such as Microsoft, Apple ,IBM, Linux, Sony just to name a few.

June 2002 - February 2004

Tuck and Sons Roofing, Congers, NY

Tuck and Son's Roofing is one of New York's premier roofing companies. I started as a Laborer with the company. Soon I would learn shingles, slate and eventually became a sales representative and estimator before moving to Las Vegas to attend the College of Southern Nevada.

Education

June 2004 - December 2005

College of Southern Nevada, Las Vegas, NV

I enrolled in the College of Southern Nevada in June 0f 2004 and studied international business until December of 2005.